[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What language was spoken in the 1987 comedy movie Moonstruck, apart from English?", "correct_answer": "Italian", "incorrect_answers": ["French", "German", "Spanish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This herb, with the scientific name Veronica officinalis, is native to Europe and Asia, and is very rich in vitamins and antioxidants.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Pauls Betony", "Heath Speedwell", "Common Gypsyweed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of what nationality is the actor who plays Pontius Pilate in the 2004 movie The Passion of the Christ?", "correct_answer": "Bulgarian", "incorrect_answers": ["Greek", "Russian", "Italian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The world\u2019s most expensive coffee, Kopi Luwak, goes through a unique harvesting process. In Indonesian, \u201ckopi\u201d means coffee and \u201cluwak\u201d means what?", "correct_answer": "Civet", "incorrect_answers": ["Mountain", "Lunar", "Sea Water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet has been demoted from its planet status by scientists like Neil Tyson, Director of the Hayden Planetarium?", "correct_answer": "Pluto", "incorrect_answers": ["Neptune", "Uranus", "Mercury"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert Todd Lincoln Beckwith was the last of the Lincoln line. When did he die?", "correct_answer": "1985", "incorrect_answers": ["1898", "1927", "1956"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you were a baker, what would you be called in Spanish?", "correct_answer": "panadero", "incorrect_answers": ["marinero", "carpintero", "cerrajero"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What component of the human eye is responsible for the perception of light of different wavelengths, which results into color vision?", "correct_answer": "Cones", "incorrect_answers": ["Rods", "None of these", "Pupils"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was given the first numbered patent in the USA?", "correct_answer": "Samuel Hopkins", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry Clinton", "Ben Franklin", "Paul Revere"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Movie producer Lorenzo di Bonaventura compared the master of Megatron from Transformers 2 to what notable historical person?", "correct_answer": "Judas Iscariot", "incorrect_answers": ["King Henry VIII of England", "Joseph Stalin", "Adolf Hitler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the place in which the main characters of Pirates of the Caribbean live?", "correct_answer": "Port Royal", "incorrect_answers": ["Royal Pointe", "Black Pearl", "England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does psephology study?", "correct_answer": "elections", "incorrect_answers": ["African snakes", "dreams", "poetry"]}]